https://www.ncura.edu/privacy.aspx

X
Membership & VolunteeringMembership CategoriesMembership BenefitsJoin NCURACollaborate NCURAVolunteeringVolunteer PositionsAwardsSalary SurveyEducationCalendarOnline EducationMeetings & ConferencesProposal SubmissionTraveling WorkshopsEducation Scholarship FundApply for Education Scholarship FundOn-Campus WorkshopsNCURA Distinguished Educator DesignationInsight Leadership GroupPodcastsPublicationsNCURA MagazinePast IssuesSubmissionsEditorsAdvertisingOnline PublicationsResearch Management ReviewAuthor InstructionsEditorial BoardArchivesStoreSponsored Research SubscriptionGlobal InitiativesAbout UsSelect Committee on Global AffairsGlobal WorkshopsNCURA Global Traveling Workshop FacultyNCURA Fellowship ProgramNCURA Fellowship Host InstitutionENRICH/Horizon 2020Horizon 2020 Workshop - AM 57Horizon 2020 Workshop - AM 58Hosting International Delegations in Washington DCNCURA Global PartnersNCURA-Cuba PartnershipNCURA Global WebinarNews and EventsInstitutional ProgramsPeer Advisory ServicesResearch Administration PlanningFocused AnalysisDirected EducationPeer Review ProgramsSponsored Programs ReviewStandardsUnit-Level ReviewStandardsGlobal ReviewStandardsResearch Compliance ReviewStandardsBenefits to Peer ReviewF.A.Q.Costs & Further InformationMeet the Reviewers-AdvisorsProgram GovernanceAra TahmassianJeff SeoBob AndresenJudy FredenbergJill TincherRoger WarehamInstitutions Using Peer ProgramsResources
Create Non-Member Account
|
Login
Privacy
Privacy
Privacy Statement
National Council of University Research Administrators is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the National Council of University Research Administrators site and governs data collection and usage. By using the National Council of University Research Administrators site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
National Council of University Research Administrators collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. National Council of University Research Administrators also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by National Council of University Research Administrators. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by National Council of University Research Administrators for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the National Council of University Research Administrators site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through National Council of University Research Administrators public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: National Council of University Research Administrators does not read any of your private online communications.
National Council of University Research Administrators encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from National Council of University Research Administrators so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. National Council of University Research Administrators is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the National Council of University Research Administrators and National Council of University Research Administrators family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
National Council of University Research Administrators collects and uses your personal information to operate the National Council of University Research Administrators Web site and deliver the services you have requested. National Council of University Research Administrators also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from National Council of University Research Administrators and its affiliates. National Council of University Research Administrators may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
National Council of University Research Administrators does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. National Council of University Research Administrators may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, National Council of University Research Administrators may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to National Council of University Research Administrators, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
National Council of University Research Administrators does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
National Council of University Research Administrators keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within National Council of University Research Administrators, in order to determine what National Council of University Research Administrators services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within National Council of University Research Administrators to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
National Council of University Research Administrators Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on National Council of University Research Administrators or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of National Council of University Research Administrators; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of National Council of University Research Administrators, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The National Council of University Research Administrators Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize National Council of University Research Administrators pages, or register with National Council of University Research Administrators site or services, a cookie helps National Council of University Research Administrators to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same National Council of University Research Administrators Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the National Council of University Research Administrators features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the National Council of University Research Administrators services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
National Council of University Research Administrators secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. National Council of University Research Administrators secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
National Council of University Research Administrators will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. National Council of University Research Administrators encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how National Council of University Research Administrators is protecting your information.
Contact Information
National Council of University Research Administrators welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that National Council of University Research Administrators has not adhered to this Statement, please contact National Council of University Research Administrators at johnson@ncura.edu. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
